<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Constellations</title>
    <link>https://mehermdsaad.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Constellations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.146.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 22:00:01 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mehermdsaad.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Architecture of Mondays</title>
      <link>https://mehermdsaad.github.io/posts/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 22:00:01 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mehermdsaad.github.io/posts/quotes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You act like mortals in all that you fear, and like immortals in all that you desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following is taken from a blog post from JA Westenberg (link)[https://www.joanwestenberg.com/your-life-is-the-sum-total-of-2-000-mondays/?ref=westenberg-newsletter]: I would like to remember this point, hence I am copying it here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-architecture-of-an-ordinary-day&#34;&gt;The architecture of an ordinary day&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your life is going to be 80% Mondays and their equivalents, the design specifications for Monday matter more than the design specifications for your vacation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Am I Not The Main Character?</title>
      <link>https://mehermdsaad.github.io/posts/aminotthemaincharacter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:19:56 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mehermdsaad.github.io/posts/aminotthemaincharacter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I think of the events of July quite often. When people rose up to the streets with stones against bullets. To an uninformed audience this might sound like legend and not real; however this is indeed what happened on the ground in the year 2024 in Bangladesh. As the police along with Chatro League started raining fire over the students and general people, the people didn&amp;rsquo;t disperse- they swelled even more. And yes, they took to the fight stones and bricks against bullets and gunpowder. The rest is history from start till the end- a month of intense one-sided fights- with shields of flesh against sharp bullets the people fought and dethroned the most vile dictator the nation has had to face.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
